(Sheldon:)So, tomorrow?
(Stuart:)I don't mean to be rude,
Sheldon, but,
(Stuart:)my life is kind of
falling apart right now.
(Sheldon:)Your life?
(Sheldon:)The university is making me
do string theory,
(Sheldon:)and my girlfriend loves me
so much she wants to live with me.
(Sheldon:)And now, the place I need to go when
I'm sad is damp and smells funny.
(Stuart:)Well, sorry I let you down.
(Sheldon:)No, I do not accept this.
(Sheldon:)Everything is changing and I hate it.
(Sheldon:)It stops now. I'm helping you
get back on your feet.
(Sheldon:)I would like to purchase
this comic book, please.
(Stuart:)That'll be $2.99.
(Sheldon:)Really? it's soaking wet.
(Stuart:)Fine, a dollar.
-Can you break a 20?
-No, I only have hundreds.
(Raj:)You know what?
(Sheldon:)I don't always recognize sarcasm,
but I do right now,
(Sheldon:)and I don't appreciate it.